BGM
One, two, three, four, five
One, two, three...
Wah!
Oh, my God.
That's a lot of food.
Wow!
Wow.
This is fun.
Where is it?
♪ BGM
Transparent, cute face.
Transparent, with a hint of red.
I'm lost.
Pretty for you
I want to make it happen with you
If it's a word, I won't let you in
It's a now, it's a bow
Hence, miso umeme
So, the ear monitors are completed!
Yay!
Wait, wait, wait.
Look!
It's in there like this.
And, Yuko.
Here comes the bento.
What? I thought it was just a gift.
I'm so happy.
You might be happy.
I can't wait to open it.
You want to open it? Oh, my God.
Let's open it.
Who do you want to open first?
Yoo-ro.
Okay, I'll go first.Okay, I'll go.
Open the package!
Ta-da!
Yucharo!
So cute!
Oh, no, I'm so nervous!
Here we go.
Wow!
Quaint.
Quaint!
It's in there, isn't it?
Sarara!
Ha! So cute!
Here we go.
This way!
So cute!
Cute!
What's with the color?
Certainly!
Cute!
I think I got it to match.
It's cute! Yuzu-ish! So cute!
I got it in pink and turquoise blue!
Cute!
It's so cute!
Write "ame-hura" on it.
And over here it says "Yuzuki".
and the one that says "Yuzuki" over here is kind of a muted purple.
I thought it would be nice to have something that was more like a pop
I thought it would be nice if there was a yuzu-like one, because I like that kind of sparkly stuff.
The two loudest colors.
Cute!So cute!
It's so cute!
Isn't it too cute?
They're so cute together.
It's so cute!
So cute!
What does it say?
Pizza!
Cute! Cute!
Pizza's cute!
It's cute.
He's so cute.
You don't even know who he is.
It's cute!
I was a little confused, but I liked the brighter light blue one.
I'm a sucker for bright, pretty colors.
I really wanted to put this one in.
So I decided to add a little bit of flowery blue to the two.
This one is a heart with a flower.
This one is a one-piece dress.
It's so cool!
It's so cute!
It's so simple!
I'm just saying, don't you like Kamoyaka stickers?
I don't have any more emojis or anything so that I can put stickers on it.
The capital letters are cute too!
Ready, go!
Ta-da!
So cute!
It's so cute!
Ta-da! Yellow and black.
It's black.
What was it?
The reason why I decided to do it...
I decided to put yellow because our member's color is yellow.The member's color is yellow, so I decided to put in yellow.
The next color was white, and I was very particular about it.
After much deliberation, I decided on this color.
I asked for everyone's opinion.
They said, "I think this color is better.
So I decided on this one!
What? I'm so excited.
Doesn't it look really good?
I'll open it.
Okay.
I went with the standard Eyler. Letters and lowercase.
I could have gone with all letters, but I kept it simple.
Okay? Yes!
I went with red and black. It's pretty ayler-ish.
Cute. I like these two.
I chose black because it's my favorite color, and red is the unofficial color of Amefura, so I went with those two colors.
I put my name "R Amefura" on the right, and my name "L Ira" on the left.
It's like... well, everyone's name. It's "Amefura".
It's so cute!
See you! I'm home!
Is it cool?
Oh, my God! Oh, man!
Super cute!
It fits so well.
Ta-da!
It looks like this
One is black
One is red.
Can you tell?
I feel like I can hear a very detailed sound.
It's like music in my ears.
It's amazing.
Once in a lifetime pop shoes!
Everybody wants to play Doraemon.
I don't have any plates or anything.
I want to show them off.I want to show you.
I don't care.
It's too much.
I'm playing Yu-Gi-Oh with my ear buds in.
If you don't touch it, it's confiscated.
I don't like it.
What do you mean?
You mean we can't use Biosize?
There's no such thing as confiscation.
I built it for Biosize.
I really...
I made it so I could use it.
Well, I don't have a choice now. I'll just play the message game.
Yeah, we'll just try.
Well, don't you just want to see how much you can't hear?
Maybe there's a theory that you can hear really well.
That's for sure.
Let's have Mayaka do it once, and Yuka-chan write it down.
I'll whisper to Mayaka like an angel.
Oh, okay.
Can you work on that for a bit?
Okay.
Can you hear me?
You okay? Can you hear me now? You can't hear me?
I can't hear you.
Well, let's try saying it.
In the shape of your mouth.
Okay. Let's go.
Chibe.
You're small.
A bruised girl.
You're cute. Really.
I love it.I love it.
You've got to be kidding me.
You're always so obvious and so targeted. You're a calculating bitch.
Thank you.
Let's talk more at the MC.
I'm telling you the truth.
You're always so fake and a real bitch.
Don't talk at the MC.
Really do your job.
She's just most of the time.
How is she as the oldest?
You're the oldest, but that day.
Everyone was howling a lot.
They were super barking.
Thank you.
It was great.
I can't hear anything.
A piece of skin
A piece of leather
I knew it!
Ichika was a genius!
I knew it ok
dare a
filmmaking
I'll do it then!
I'll stand regarding
Ichika's a genius!
He's a genius!
That's right!
Ichika is a genius!
Say it slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly...
Ichika's a genius!Ichika was a genius after all
Ichika was a genius.
Deppies?
Ichika is...
I knew it!
Debauchery?
Yes, yes...
I knew it!
Genius.
Idiot? It's the other way around.
Why did you have to make it two words?
Genius.
Crushed?
White crush?
Genius.
Wait a minute... I'm still a genius.
Genius? I knew it.
Ichika's a genius.
I knew it!
Don't be silly. Don't be silly.
I didn't say that.
What? Don't play games with me.
What? What? What?
What?
Ichika's a genius.
Okay, I think she's here.
Ichika was a genius.
Wow!
I'm going home now!
Thank you very much!
That's a lot of work.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm sorry to hear that you were all nervous about receiving the vile sign.I'm sorry to hear that you all got nervous when you received the vile sign.
Let's go for it!
Wow!